One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
I grabbed hold, digging in my claws
te ni totte tsume o tateta
but the future
sono mirai wa
blurred together, colors running
nijimu iro ni kasunde mieta
A red that can swallow even summer's hues
natsu no iro mo nuritsubusu you na aka ni
bokura no koe kakikesareteiku you de
now attempts to blot out our voices
Move those halting feet of yours
tachidomaru sono ashi o fumidasou ze
Don't let stand the lies for show
misekake no uso yarisugosu yori
I'll give up countless mornings for my vows
nandome no asa chikai to hikikaeru yo
For the dream that we shared
bokura ga miteita yume
Labophase
Stussy...
It’s me...
Edison!
Deactivate da barrier and run...
Wha?
I can’t! I don’t want anything to happen
to the Straw Hats before they leave.
Honestly... Da barrier ain’t doin’ us
no good no more.
Not against these folks
who can just get past it anyway...
Ah’ve already done my best
to ensure da Straw Hats’ escape.
Dey’ll manage da rest, somehow.
Good to know.
If they don’t make it,
Stella would hate me.
Nah, he wouldn’t.
But ya gotta get out now!
But...
I’m stumped...
Now without Stella,
I don’t know who to live for...
anymore...
Jinbe, why aren’t you here yet?!
Sorry! We’re almost there.
You don’t gotta apologize, Jinbe.
We’re running as fast as we can.
You say something, Zoro?!
I’m kicking your ass later!
Hurry up! Ships are starting to converge
off the northeast coast.
I don’t wanna be under attack
as soon as we land on the water!
Let’s move, then!
That old fart can cut through anything!
Don’t let him use his sword!
Concassé!
Go to hell, geezer!
Wha—
Life-form detected...
Bonney!
Whoa!
My future form
doesn’t last for long...
C’mon, now...
Don’t push yourself too far!
We can’t drop our guard!
Stinkin’ old guy...!
Nuh?!
Where’s he going?!
The Void Century...
came to an end
with Joyboy’s defeat.
How long do you intend to
prattle on, Vegapunk?!
It ended, leaving behind...
the incalculable,
irreparable ravages of war...
Obnoxious life-form!
Our world is made up of
a series of islands.
Crossing the seas poses difficulties,
so many people spend their entire lives
without exploring foreign cultures.
Why is he stating the obvious now?
The seas are simply too dangerous.
But this common
understanding of the world...
does not necessarily apply to
the world of a thousand years ago.
A cataclysm during the Void Century...
caused the world...
to sink into the sea once before.
We’re now living atop scattered pieces of
what were once continents.
The world sank into the sea?!
Atop scattered pieces of continents?!
The world from a millennium ago
is now ruined, lying at the bottom of the sea.
It is believed that, in ancient times,
there were several continents
in the world of which we have no record.
This is quite a revelation.
Hey! Where are you going, Nojiko?
The world is in danger...
Fill me in later.
I’m going to check on
the tangerine field.
Nojiko!
If the world hadn’t changed at all
from the past,
erasing all traces of a century of history
from the records would be impossible.
It makes much more sense,
however, if...
you consider that, in a mere hundred years,
the sea level rose by the astonishing amount of...
two hundred meters!
What?! T-T-Two hundred meters?!
Even this massive warship
is only sixty meters long!
No wonder the whole world vanished...
Dammit, men!
Don’t just stand around listening to the speech!
We’ve got Cipher Pol and Seraphim
falling out of the sky!
Rescue them, now!
Mock
Town,
Town of
Ridicule
You hearin’ this guy?!
He just keeps comin’ up with this stuff!
The old fart’s a total riot!
How’s that even possible?!
Sakura
Kingdom
(Chopper's
homeland)
How does such a thing happen?
This world of ours
still has so much wonder in it!
That mountain is just about
two hundred meters high.
That’s how high the sea level rose?
Sounds like hell...
How many people would die from that?!
Water
Seven,
City of
Water
Why did the sea level rise
during that century, then?
It stands to reason that the cause
would be an unexpected natural calamity.
But I’m certain
the disaster was man-made.
There’s just no freakin’ way!
Were such a cataclysm
caused by natural forces,
the initial disaster would have spanned
several centuries...
and inflicted slow
but continuous damage upon the world.
That can’t be true! I don’t buy it!
But by any measurement — climatology, geology,
environmental and atmospheric science —
this dramatic shift could not have happened
within a single century!
Therefore, the cause
must be something else.
When I detected the rise
in worldwide sea levels the other day,
I had my answer.
I knew the cause,
and confirmed its existence!
The Ancient Weapons that sank the world
eight hundred years ago still exist,
and await the day
they are once again activated!
That is to say, the great war
that erupted during the Void Century...
has not yet ended!
You gotta be kidding!
The weapons that sank the world
are still out there somewhere?!
The war from eight hundred years ago
is still ongoing?
Where?!
No one from back then is still alive!
How can a war be ongoing
if nobody knows about it, Vegapunk?!
I...
must apologize deeply.
But I need you to know this!
I wanted to create a source of power
essential for the future growth of this world’s industries.
It is still incomplete, however!
The Mother Flame, the culmination of my research,
has just reached the stage of practical use!
It is a power source that will surely enrich
the lives of people in all countries someday!
However...
a fragment of that flame
was stolen one day.
It’s all my fault.
Cipher Pol agents
are at the center of the island?!
It’s impossible to rescue them!
The whole island’s covered in flames!
It’s shaking so much!
What happened, Edison?!
Scared me, too.
It’s a mess...
Da Labophase’s underground lab and
Cipher Pol agents came fallin’ to da ground.
We’ve been beat...
Ah can’t send no more Island Clouds
for da Straw Hats.
What do you mean they fell?!
One of those crazy Five Elders
is headin’ yer way!
You gotta run, Stussy. Please.
Can I release Kaku, then, Edison?
Wha?
He and Lucci may
face punishment for this.
I won’t let him chase
after the Straw Hats,
but I know full well
what he will do next.
Ah understand, Stussy.
Ah’m sorry Ah put ya through all that...
Y’all were friends, yeah?
Ah feel bad for makin’ ya betray them.
But still, ya helped us.
Ya really care about both them and us.
Feelin’ conflicted proves that
yer human, Stussy.
Live your life however you want
from now on,
but promise me yer gonna survive!
I will!
Roughly two weeks
after the flame was stolen,
we received word of a violent flash in
the skies over Lulusia...
Lulusia...
followed by intel that the kingdom
had vanished without a trace.
Somebody destroyed Lulusia?!
And what’s more, after that, we observed
the signs of an imminent worldwide quake.
As a scientist,
and with pride in my development...
That was caused by one of
the Ancient Weapons?!
Kingdom of
Prodence
Nothing but the Mother Flame could have
created such an immense amount of energy!
The Kingdom of Lulusia is gone?!
We haven’t received such information.
Verify it, immediately!
Yes, sire!
The flame that I created...
was used to activate
an Ancient Weapon!
I have absolutely no idea
who carried it out,
but the results speak for themselves!
I was complicit
in the taking of numerous lives.
As such, I feel personally responsible!
I am truly sorry!
The artificial catastrophe
that once sank this world...
has been shown to be possible.
Vegapunk! It’s not your fault!
Flower Capital
Land of Wano
What?!
Then Pluton is—
Momonosuke-sama!
I implore you to mind your words!
Understood. My apologies.
Buggy
District
Emptee Bluffs
Island
New World
In the past,
there were three Ancient Weapons,
and Joyboy sought to pass them on
to future generations.
Why did he do that?
Did he want the world to sink more?
Who is evil and who is good?!
There will be a time
when all the answers come clear!
You’re going to choke.
I told you, you silly man...
And I warn you, that moment will happen
when we reach the very precipice of the world’s drowning!
The Void Century
still remains full of unknowns.
But, there are people
who have learned the whole truth!
You really are going to
spill the beans, huh,
Vegapunk?!
The Pirate King’s crew.
What?!
Pirates?!
Why?!
Why are the secrets of the world
in the hands of pirates?!
It’s too dangerous!
Huh?
Wait a minute.
That’s strange.
Stella, how’d you know
I stole the Mother Flame?
The synchronization was turned off.
You wouldn’ta found me out!
I know you as a terrible liar and actor!
At that moment...
York!
Is this all your doing?!
You were truly shocked!
You received word of Lulusia
and observed the data?
What does that mean?
When?
The timeline doesn’t add up!
You knew what the Government would do?
But if that’s the case,
then I had it all wrong!
He wouldn’t do something half-assed
like just hiding the Transmission Transponder Snail!
Five Elders!
I know where
the Transmission Transponder Snail is!
Are you certain?
I am!
I’s a Vegapunk, too!
The Transmission Transponder Snail
is in the Fabriophase,
protected by the Iron Giant!
No good! Nothing’s working!
Why did those who learned the truth
fade away without telling anyone anything?
Why didn’t they act on it?
Ray-san.
You’re drinking too much.
Well, I’m just another old man now.
It’s not like you to be this wiped out...
And you’re telling them too much, Vegapunk...
Us old folk should keep our secrets...
and not ruin it for the young’uns,
you damn fool...
Right, Roger?
Let the kids have their fun...
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop beep-beep-beep-bup-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipii pipopii, pipopiipii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep
Piipapii papipo, piipapii
No No No No No norenai
No, no, no, no, no, not feelin' it
kobiritsuichatte mou odorenai
I'm all stiff, all outta dances
My head feels so good, 'f I get unlucky again
atama Feel so good, mata Unlucky demo
Cola de fukitobase yowaki o
just gonna blow away the shy with a cola
Hey all you boys & girls! Looking good!
soko no Boys & Girls! omae ii yatsu
Hey all you boys & girls!
soko no Boys & Girls!
Update failed. I've had enough!
appudeto wa shippai kori gori
Wasn't it OK 'til yesterday?
kinou made nara seikai?
La la la la la la, run, run, run...
ran ran ran ran ran ran Run Run Run
"Hiding yet?"
mou ii kai?
You ready yet, up for a dance
junbi wa douyo odoreru no?
bukkowareteru kono jidai
in this broken era?
"Come find us!"
mou ii yo!
Spread out from here, drop into the world
koko kara kakusan sekai e Drop
Let loose on the stage of freedom and liberation
jiyuu to kaihou no Stage e
Those rising heads're punks!!!!!! No way!!!
wakiagaru atama ga Punk!!!!!! No way!!!
Sick of waitin', goof off and dance
matenaiyo fuzaketa Dance
Dopamine spilling over
afuredasu dopamin
The lonely singing in unity
kodoku ga tsudoi utau koushin
Bip-bip-bip-bup-bup-bup-bup-bupping
pipipi papapapapatteru
Can't can't can't count me out yet
mada mada mada horobinai
There's some stranger waving me over
shiranai dareka ga temaneki da
Smilin' so wide that it can't be real
uso mitai ni waratteru